I, Clayton, take you,
Isabelle, to be my wife,
to have and to hold from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer or for poorer,
in sickness and health,
to love and to cherish,
until death do us part, according
to God's holy intent, and I promise,
and I promise you
my lifelong faithfulness.
And I promise you
Awesome.
Isabelle, repeat this after me.
I, Isabelle.
Take you, Clayton.
To be my husband.
To have and to hold.
From this day forward.
For better or for worse.
For richer or for poorer.
For richer or poorer.
In sickness and in health.
To love and to cherish.
To love and to cherish, until death do
us part, according to God's holy intent,
and I promise you
my lifelong faithfulness.
And I promise you